An official website of the United States government

Here’s how you know

Here’s how you know

**Official websites use .gov**  
A **.gov** website belongs to an official government organization in the United States.

**Secure .gov websites use HTTPS**  
A **lock** ( Lock A locked padlock ) or **https://** means you’ve safely connected to the .gov website. Share sensitive information only on official, secure websites.

Explore Census.gov for...

Search data, events, resources, and more

Search

      Search

* * *

* * *

Helpful Links

* * *

Helpful Links

Search

Menu

* * *

Topics

Browse our topics and subtopics to find information and data.

Data & Maps

Access demographic, economic and population data from the U.S. Census Bureau. Explore census data with visualizations and view tutorials.

Surveys & Programs

Our surveys provide periodic and comprehensive statistics about the nation. This data is critical for government programs, policies, and decision-making.

Resource Library

Browse our collection of stories and more.

Topics

Data & Maps

Surveys & Programs

Resource Library

* * *

Topics

Data & Maps

Surveys & Programs

Resource Library

* * *

* * *

* * *

* * *

* * *

* * *

//* [Census.gov](https://www.census.gov/en.html) /
* [About the Bureau](https://www.census.gov/about-us) /
* [Policies and Notices](https://www.census.gov/about/policies.html) /
* Data Protection and Privacy Policy

Data Protection and Privacy Policy
==================================

Within Policies and Notices

Data Protection and Privacy Policy
==================================

We are committed to handling your information responsibly. Your information is kept confidential.  This commitment applies to the individuals, households, and businesses that answer our surveys, and to those browsing our website.

Featured
--------

* * * *
    
    [Online Privacy Policy
    
    Information on children's online privacy, data retention, document accessibility, info collected from e-mail and online forms, and third party websites.](https://www.census.gov/about/policies/privacy/privacy-policy.html "Online Privacy Policy")
    
    * * *
    
* * * *
    
    [Data Stewardship
    
    Information about the Census Bureau's data stewardship program.](https://www.census.gov/about/policies/privacy/data_stewardship.html "Data Stewardship")
    
    * * *
    
* * * *
    
    [Our Privacy Principles
    
    Information about the U.S. Census Bureau's privacy principles.](https://www.census.gov/about/policies/privacy/data_stewardship/our_privacy_principles.html "Our Privacy Principles")
    
    * * *

Survey Information
------------------

* * * *
    
    [Are You in a Survey? Help for Survey Participants
    
    Did the Census Bureau contact you about participating in a survey? This site provides answers about our surveys and who to contact for more information.](https://www.census.gov/programs-surveys/surveyhelp.html "Are You in a Survey?  Help for Survey Participants")
    
    * * *
    
* * * *
    
    [Our Surveys & Programs
    
    Our surveys provide periodic and comprehensive statistics about the nation. This data is critical for government programs, policies, and decision-making.](https://www.census.gov/programs-surveys.html "Our Surveys & Programs")
    
    * * *

Checking the Facts
------------------

* * * *
    
    [Trust & Safety Team
    
    Learn how the Trust & Safety Team helps you get the facts about our surveys and censuses and fights misinformation and disinformation.](https://www.census.gov/about/trust-and-safety.html "Trust & Safety Team")
    
    * * *
    
* * * *
    
    [Fighting Census Rumors
    
    Learn how the U.S. Census Bureau's Trust & Safety Team protected the 2020 Census count by reporting inaccurate, suspicious, and fraudulent information.](https://www.census.gov/newsroom/rumors.html "Fighting Census Rumors")
    
    * * *

Page Last Revised - October 22, 2024

✕

Is this page helpful?  

 Yes  No

✕

NO THANKS

255 characters maximum 255 characters maximum reached

✕

Thank you for your feedback.  
Comments or suggestions?  

Top

Receive Updates

To sign up for updates please enter your email address.

   Enter your email address  Subscribe

* * *

Stay Current

Stay Connected

Follow

[](https://www.facebook.com/uscensusbureau/ "Facebook")[](https://twitter.com/uscensusbureau/ "X (Twitter)")[](https://www.linkedin.com/company/us-census-bureau/ "Linkedln")[](https://www.youtube.com/user/uscensusbureau/ "YouTube")[](https://www.instagram.com/uscensusbureau/ "Instagram")

* * *

Measuring America's People, Places, and Economy
